HEKWANG LHI

Paramus, NJ 07652

Phone: 551-587-8177 | Email: hekwang.lhi@gmail.com
LinkedIn: /hekwanglhi | Github: /klhi | Portfolio:/react-portfolio/

SUMMARY

Full Stack Web Developer with a background in Computer Engineering and job experiences in different positions and areas. Effective at combining creativity and problem resolving to develop user-friendly applications. Known among staff for strong wit and attention to detail no matter the complexity of the project, and recently earned a Certificate in Coding from Columbia University, New York.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

HTML5, CSS, JQuery, Javascript, API, JSON, AJAX, Express, React, Node, Bootstrap, C, Python, PHP, Java, C++, SQL, MySQL, MongoDB, Barcode, Item Code, Label, Inventory

PROJECTS

Fitness Tracker | note-taker-khli3.heroku | Full Stack and Designer

 Note Taker that can be used to write and save notes. This application uses an Express.js back end and saves and retrieves note data from a JSON file

Redux Store | redux-store-v.heroku | Backend and Designer

• E-commerce platform uses Redux to manage global state instead of the Context API and this website's state management is out of the React ecosystem

Team Profile Generator | github-team-profile-generators | Sole Developer

build a Node.js command-line application that takes in information about employees on a software
engineering team, then generates an HTML webpage that displays summaries for each person and
a unit test for every part of code and ensure that it passes each test using Javascript, Node.js, OOP

EXPERIENCE

Office Manager 2019-2021

Yamato Sushi Catering, Inc., New Jersey

- Processed sales orders and production orders for shifts in Online and Excel. Sustained in compliance to HACCP plan and related licenses.
- Purchased materials and maintained inventories, supplies and equipment.

Operation Coordinator

2017-2019

Aviance Hair Corp., New Jersey

- Processed sales orders, managed item properties, created invoices and managed inflow and outflow of shipments. Resolved all order discrepancies. Organized and maintained office records.
- Supported customers from Central and South America, Mexico, and Canada.
- Analyzed weekly, monthly, and annual sales and warehouse performance. Maintained inventories.
- Prepared, drafted, and negotiated shipment rates with UPS, FedEx, and trucking companies.
- Created and updated work process manuals

Office Assistant 2014-2016

Bethel Industries Inc., New Jersey

- Developed and maintained the time attendance system based on web coded by python and mysql.
- Maintained machines and parts status data for repairs and scheduled with engineers.

- Recruited new hires and ensured forms/documents. Answered all inquiries for multinationals.
- Worked with payroll company: Reconciled overtime, health insurance, deductions, sick days, and other data accurately and created reports. Personnel management pertaining to sick leave, discretionary time, and discrepancies in timecards.
- Supported production department for compliance with ISO 9000 standards.
- Performed all other office duties. Maintained and organized documents and records properly.

Risk/Chargeback Analyst

2010-2013

United Merchant Service, Inc., New Jersey

- Processed chargeback disputes and analyzed and determined appropriate responses.
- Analyzed risk factors, patterns, and policies to reduce loss. Recorded details of inquiries, complaints, comments, and action taken from all merchants, card holders and bank interactions.

EDUCATION

Certificate - Coding, Bootcamp, Engineering School, Columbia University

A 12-week full time intensive program focused on gaining technical programming skills in JavaScript, MySQL, MongoDB, MERN Stack, Progressive Web Applications, HTML5, CSS, JavaScript, jQuery, Bootstrap, Heroku, Git, API, JSON, AJAX, Quality Assurance (Unit Testing, Linting, Continuous Integration), Python, Java, Amazon Web Services

Summer Course - Advanced PHP with MySQL, NYU School of Continuing and Professional Studies 2014 Computer Engineering, Computer Science Department, University of Chile, Santiago, Chile Bachelor of Science - Computer Science, Computer Science Department, University of Chile, Stgo, Chile